MUHAMMED KHALED

Proactive and creative professional with high technical skills and eight years track record of delivering excellent customer service and achieving a variety of targets.

CONTACT ME HERE:

Mobile: +447366666896

Email: 2014419@leedstrinity.ac.uk Address: Meanwood Road, Leeds Portfolio: www.muhammedkhaled.com

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am currently a final year computer science student on track to achieve a first-class degree in summer 2021. During my studies, I have been freelancing and working with several high-end brands such as Printwell, Utility Warehouse, Samsung, and more. Within this time, I have amassed a wealth of experience and skills across technical support, software development, UI/UX design, customer service, business operations, leadership, and management.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science . LTU - 2021
HND in Computing . CCL - 2020
HNC in Computing. Nescot- 2019
Foundation in Business and Computing . LBIC - 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

The Complete Web Development - Zero To Mastery Academy Google IT Support Professional - Google . Pending UI/UX Design - Interaction Design Foundation . Pending

CORE SKILLS

- Multilingual (English Arabic and Spanish) Technical Knowledge Problem Solving High Attention to Details Project Management
- Capable of Achieving Targets Ability to Follow Instructions Unique Customer Service & Customer Engagement Project Management

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Front-End:

HTML, CSS, Bulma, Sass, Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJS, jQuery, Vue, and Bootstrap.

Backend:

Python (Flask), Machine Learning, Firebase, Firestore, MongoDB, MySQL, NodeJS, PHP, Rest APIs, and Google APIs.

CMS:

WordPress and Catfish.

Tools:

git, GitLab, Github, npm, yarn, Adobe XD, Photoshop, and Canvas.

UI/UX DESIGN

- Research User Personas Storyboards Customer maps
- Brainstorming User Flows Site maps Low-fidelity prototype
- hand-drawn sketches High-fidelity prototypes interactive prototypes
- Usability Reports Analytics Reports

TECHNICAL SUPPORT

- Microsoft Office Packages, Office 365 administration and Microsoft operating systems administration.
- Active Directory, Networking TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, VPN, LAN, Switch management and SCCM.
- Maintaining backups and printer management.
- Cybersecurity

LATEST WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Software Developer - UI Design - Technical Support

Printwell (UK) LTD . Freelance

Mar 2020 - Present . 1 yr

In charge of the full process of the design, development research, and system switch of all Printwell Digital stores along with their products and product redesign and technical support:

- Software Development: designing and developing Printwell's all closed and open online stores
- UI Design: wireframes, high-fidelity prototypes, and testing.
- Product Design: designing all Printwell's Web to Print products using JavaScript and PS.
- Technical Support: communicating with clients and solving their issues through emails and phone calls

Software Developer - UI/UX Designer - IT Consultant

Zinrack . Freelance . Co founder

Feb 2017- Present . 4 yr 1 mo

While freelancing under Zinrack, I offer many services and worked with various brands. My role is very diverse, some of the responsibilities I have are the following:

- Designing, developing and leading small and big projects including front-end and back-end.
- Conducting UX research including user personas, user journeys, and site maps.
- Designing high and low fidelity prototypes along with wireframes.
- Graphic designing of various artworks such as logos, banners, and other marketing materials.
- Communicating with clients and solving their issues through emails and phone calls.
- Designing and maintaining WordPress and Catfish websites (E-commerce and others).

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service & Compliance Officer

Synergy Prime LTD . Employed . Call Centre

Feb 2019 - Jan 2020. 1 yr

Managing a team of 12 agents and ensuring that they all meet their KPI targets in terms of customer service, sales, and compliance:

- Monitoring, scoring and documenting agents' calls.
- Giving Feedback to agents in terms of customer service and sales.
- Ensure agents to remain compliant with the regulating bodies such as the FCA.
- Answering customers escalated calls and solving complex issues.
- Preforming a variety of data entry tasks.
- Processing information and writing and filling weekly and daily reports.

Sales Rep

London City Tour . Employed . Call Centre Mar 2018 - Jan 2020. 1 yr

Project Manager

Tadom Hill Resorts . Employed . Malaysia sep 2016 - Mar 2017 . 7 mo

Receptionist

Menu Lodge . Employed . Malaysia Feb 2015 - Jan 2016 . 11 mo

Team Member

Krispy Kreme . Employed Sep 2017- Jun 2018 . 9 mo

Personal Assistant

Bamboo Village . Employed . Malaysia Jan 2016 - Aug 2016 . 6 mo